A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1974-2006.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction,
1974-2006.
The Library of Virginia
39607, 51086, 51198
Virginia. Dept. of Education.
273 cu. ft.
Unprocessed.
Acquisition Information
Accession 39607 was transferred by Parker, Michelle - Dept. of Education, 101 14th Street, Richmond, Va. 23219, 05/28/02
Virginia. -- Dept. of Education.
Virginia. -- Dept. of Education.
Education -- Virginia.
Public schools -- Virginia.
School superintendents -- Virginia.
Letters (correspondence) -- aat.
State government records -- Virginia. -- aat.
Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1974-2006, are housed in XX boxes and are arranged in original order. Records related to all aspects of public school education in Virginia. General correspondence includes correspondence with school divisions, associations, councils, commissions, committees, organizations, state government and federal government. Also includes Central Office files and correspondence with Dept. of Education departments and divisions, and other staff. May contain correspondence, conference materials, meeting records, publications, speeches, and reports.
Includes records for the following Superintendents of Public Instruction: Dr. W.E. Campbell, Dr. S. John Davis.
Southeastern Regional Council for Educational Improvement records, 1982-1986, inlcude minutes of the Board of Directors, Executive Committee and Steering Committee. Also includes agendas, correspondence, publications and reports.
Contents List
- Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction (Accession 39607), 1974-2006., Extent: xx boxes. (Box 1-xx)
  - State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (Dr. S. John Davis), 1984-1985.
    - Appointment, 1984 June. (Box 1a)
    - Minutes and meeting records, 1984 Sept. (Box 1a)
    - Minutes and meeting records, 1984 Oct. (Box 1a)
    - Minutes and meeting records, 1984 Nov. (Box 1a)
    - Minutes and meeting records, 1985 Jan. (Box 1a)
    - Minutes and meeting records, 1985 July. (Box 1a)
  - Central Office memos, 1962-1976.
    - Memoranda (4196-6547), 1962-1972. (Box 1a)
    - Memoranda (6555-6894), 1972-1973. (Box 1a)
    - Memoranda (6977-7323), 1974. (Box 1a)
    - Memoranda (7354-7743), 1975. (Box 1a)
    - Memoranda (7763-7964), 1976. (Box 1a)
  - Southeastern Regional Council for Educational Improvement, 1982-1986.
    - Summary, undated. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 Jan-Mar. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 June. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 July. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 Aug. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 Sept. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 Oct. (Box 26a)
    - Steering Committee, 1983. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 Nov. (Box 26a)
    - Board of Directors / Executive Committee, 1983 Nov. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1983 Dec. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Jan. (Box 26a)
    - Steering Committee, 1984 Jan. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Feb. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Mar. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Apr. (Box 26a)
    - Steering Committee, 1984 Apr. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 May. (Box 26a)
    - Board of Directors, 1984 May. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 June. (Box 26a)
    - Steering Committee, 1984 July. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Aug. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Sept. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Oct. (Box 26a)
    - Steering Committee, 1984 Oct. (Box 26a)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Nov. (Box 26b)
    - Board of Directors, 1984 Nov. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Dec. (Box 26b)
    - Background papers, 1984 Dec. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Jan. (Box 26b)
    - Background papers, 1985 Jan. (Box 26b)
    - Steering Committee, 1985 Jan. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Feb. (Box 26b)
    - Executive Committee, 1985 Feb. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Mar. (Box 26b)
    - Background papers, 1985 Mar. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Apr. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 May. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 June. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 July. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Aug. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Sept. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Oct. (Box 26b)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Dec-1986 Feb. (Box 26b)
    - Occaisional Papers in Educational Polcy Analysis: No. 8 Report and Evaluation of Current Information Regarding Teacher Supply and Demand, 1984 Feb. (Box 26b)
    - Occaisional Papers in Educational Polcy Analysis: No. 410 Competencies of Effective Principals and Strategies for Implementation, 1984 Nov. (Box 26b)
    - Occaisional Papers in Educational Polcy Analysis: No. 411 Strategic Considerations for Improving the Principalship, 1984 Nov. (Box 26b)
    - Occaisional Papers in Educational Polcy Analysis: No. 412 Supplemental Employment Among Alabama Teachers, 1984 Sept. (Box 26b)
    - Occaisional Papers in Educational Polcy Analysis: No. 413 A Case Study of the Teacher Labor Market in the Southeast, 1984 Nov. (Box 26b)
    - Occaisional Papers in Educational Polcy Analysis: No. 414 Teacher Attrition in a Metropolitan School System in the Southeast, 1985 Apr. (Box 26b)
  - State Board of Education, 1972-1982.
    - News clippings concerning the State Board of Education, 1972-1978. (Box 2a)
    - Charles City County - Appointment of Division Superintendent, 1973. (Box 2a)
    - Charles City County and Emporia - Appointment of Division Superintendent, 1973. (Box 2a)
    - Charles City County and Emporia - Correspondence, 1973. (Box 2a)
    - Professional Relations Committee, 1973. (Box 2a)
    - By-laws and regulations, 1980. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1974 Jan. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1974 Apr. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendix A from permanent minutes, 1974 May. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendix C from permanent minutes, 1974 June. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1974 Aug. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1974 Sept. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1974. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1974 Dec. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1975 May. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1975 June. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1975 Aug. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1975 Oct. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1975 Dec. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1976 Jan. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1976 Feb. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1976 Mar. (Box 2a)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1976 Apr. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1976 May. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1981 Apr. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1981 May. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1981 June. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1981 July. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1981 Sept. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1981 Oct. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1981 Dec. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 Jan. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 Feb. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 Mar. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 Apr. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 May. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 June. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 July. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 Sept. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 Oct. (Box 2b)
    - Minutes - Appendices from permanent minutes, 1982 Dec. (Box 2b)
    - Amended Annual Program Plan for FY1978, 1977 June. (Box 2b)
    - Elementary and Secondary Schools - Public/Private, 1977 Apr. (Box 2b)
    - Accredited Elementary and Secondary Schools - Public/Private, 1978 Apr. (Box 2b)
    - Adult Education Annual Program Plan, 1978 Apr. (Box 2b)
    - Amendments to the Annual Program Plan for Special Education, 1978 Mar. (Box 2b)
    - Management of Virginia State Government (publication), 1975 Nov. (Box 2a)
    - Membership agreement - Williamsburg/James City County/Vocational, 1976 June. (Box 2b)
    - Public hearing - Length of the School Day, 1976 Oct 28. (Box 2a)
    - Report of Public Education - Board approved, 1977 Oct. (Box 2b)
    - Sixth Annual Evaluation Report - The Need: Education with Marketable Skills (publication), 1975 Dec. (Box 2a)
    - Test scores (1977-1978), 1978 Feb. (Box 2b)
    - Virginia State Advisory Board on Vocational Education - 8th Annual Evaluation Report, 1978 Jan. (Box 2b)
    - Virginia State Plan for Vocational Education (publication), 1975-1976. (Box 2a)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. W. E. Campbell), 1977-1978.
    - Dr. Richard L. Boyer - Special Assistant for Program Development, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Dr. Gerald Bracye - Director, Program Evaluation and Testing, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Dale Robinson - Program Planning, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Isabelle Rucker - School for the Gifted, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - C.E. Clear - Educational Research, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Harry L. Smith - Special Assistant for Public Information and Publications, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Dr. Carl L. Riehm - Assistant Superintendent of Instruction, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Bernard Taylor - Director, Division of Elementary Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Elementary Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - J.T. Micklem - Director, Division of Special Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Special Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Special Education - Appeals, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Secondary Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Adult Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Art Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Community Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Driver Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Foreign Language Service, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - History, Government and Geography, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Music Education Service, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Science Education Service, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Dr. Melvin H. Garner - Director, Division of Vocational Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Vocational Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Agricultural Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Business Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Home Economics Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Industrial Arts Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Trade and Industrial Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Assistant Superintendent for Professional and Education Support Services, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Mr. Alonzo Monday - Director, Division of Support Services, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Bureau of Teaching Materials, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Film Production Service, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Guidance Service, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - School Building Service, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Teacher Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Dr. Robert V. Turner - Special Assistant for Federal Programs, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Title I, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Title I - Funds, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Title IV, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Kruse v. Campbell, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Attorney General's Office, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Appropriations Committee, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of the Budget, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Engineering and Buildings, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Governor's Office, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Governor's Office - Miscellaneous, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Secretary of Administration, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Secretary of Education, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Secretary of Human Affairs, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Highway Safety, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Intergovernmental Affairs, Dept. of, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Division of Justice and Crime Prevention, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
    - Orange County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - P - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Proprietary Schools, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Page County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Patrick County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Petersburg, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Poquoson, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Portsmouth, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Powhatan County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Prince Edward County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Prince George County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Prince William County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Pulaski County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Presentations on proposed budget at public hearing, 1977 Aug 18. (Box 4)
    - Q - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - R - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Radford, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Rappahannock County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Richmond City, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Richmond County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Roanoke City, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Roanoke County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Rockbridge County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Rockingham County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Russell County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - S - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - School Board member appointments, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - State Departments of Educations, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Superintendent's Advisory Council, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Superintendent's Study Group, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Salem, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Saltville, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Scott County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Shenandoah County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Smyth County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Southampton County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - South Boston, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Stafford County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Staunton, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Suffolk, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Surry County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Sussex County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - T - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Tazewell County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - U - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - U.S. Congress, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - U.S. Commission on Education, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - V-General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Association of School Administrators (VASA), 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Council of Higher Education, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Education Association (VEA), 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Manufacturing Association, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Municipal League, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Virginia Beach, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - W - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Warren County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Washington County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Waynesboro, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Westmoreland County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - West Point, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Williamsburg, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Winchester, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Wise County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Wythe County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - X-Y-Z - General, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - York County, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Dept. of Education, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Directors and staff, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Dr. W.E. Campbell, Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Dr. W.H. Cochran, Deputy Superintendent of Instruction, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - School Food Service, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office / School Desegregation - Dr. V. Wendell Hylton, Special Assistant for School Integration Services, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office / School Desegregation - School Integration Services, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Mr. F. Brent Sandidge, Assistant Superintendent for Administration and Finance, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Office of Administration and Finance, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Mr. T.J. Bise, Division of Finance, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Letter of Notification, Indirect Cost Allocation Plan (to localities), 1977-1978. (Box 4)
    - Central Office - Dr. Everett B. Howerton, Jr., Assistant Superintendent for Administrative Field Services, 1977-1978. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. W. E. Campbell), 1978-1979.
    - A- General, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - American Association of School Administrators, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Annual Conference of Division Superintendents, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Applications - Miscellaneous, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Administration, Director of, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Albemarle County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Alexandria, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Arlington County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Augusta County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - B - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Bath County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Bedford County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Bland County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Bristol, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Buchanan County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Buckingham County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Bypass Services for Eligible Educationally Deprived Children, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - C - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Centex (Center for Excellence, Inc.), 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Central Office Staff meetings, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council of Chief State School Officers - Overseas trip to Indonesia and Thailand, 1978 Sept. (Box 5a)
    - Colleges and Universities, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Colleges and Universities - University of Virginia, Dr. John Sanderson presentation on development of tests to the Board of Education, 1979 Mar. (Box 5a)
    - Caroline County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Carroll County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Charlotte County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Charlottesville, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Chesapeake, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Chesterfield County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Clarke County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Clifton Forge, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Colonial Beach, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Colonial Heights, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Covington, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Committee on Special Education, Advisory, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Committee on Teacher Education, Virginia Advisory, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council on Nutrition Education and Training Programs, Advisory, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council for Title IV, Advisory, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council of Vocational Education, National Advisory, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council for Vocational Education, Virginia Advisory, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Community Education Advisory Committee, Virginia, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Commission - Virginia Independence Bicentennial, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council on State Legislation, Virginia, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Council for the Deaf, Virginia, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - D - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Danville, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Dickenson County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - E - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Education Commission of the States, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Environment, Council on the - Procedures Manual and Guidelines for the Environmental Impact Statement Program, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Executive Orders, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - F - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Finance, Subcommittee on, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Fairfax County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Federal and State Regulations for Special Education - School Division comments on, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Fauquier County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Fluvanna County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Frederick County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Fredericksburg, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - G - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - General Assembly, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - General Assembly - House of Delegates, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - General Assembly - Legislation, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - General Assembly - Legislative summary, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Granville P. Meade Scholarship, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Great American Achievements Program, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Galax, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Goochland County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Grayson County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - Greensville County, 1978-1979. (Box 5a)
    - H - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Halifax County - South Boston, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Hampton, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Henrico County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Henry County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Hopewell, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - I - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Isle of Wight County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - J - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - K - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - King George County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - King William County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - L - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Lee County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Lexington, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Loudoun County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Louisa County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Lynchburg, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - M - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Marsh and McLennan, Inc. (Liability Insurance), 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Madison County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Manassas City, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Manassas Park, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Martinsville, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Mathews County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Mecklenburg County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Montgomery County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - N - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - National Child Labor Committee, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education - Future conference, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - National Education Association, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - New Kent County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Newport News, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Norfolk, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Northampton County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Norton, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - O - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Out of State travel, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Orange County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - P - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Pilot Study Programs, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Patrick County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Petersburg, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Portsmouth, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Powhatan County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Prince William County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Pulaski County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - R - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Radford, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Rappahannock County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Richmond County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Roanoke City, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Roanoke County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Rockbridge County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Rockingham County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Russell County, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - S - General, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - School Board - Appointment of members, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - State Departments of Education, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)
    - Superintendent's Advisory Council, 1978-1979. (Box 5b)